<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/apps/libraries/libxml
	</ratings>
	<space>
		17973248
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.xmlsoft.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		2.9.0
	</version>
	<mod>3</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	<release_date>09-11-2012</release_date>
	
	<requires>zlib</requires>
	<requires>libiconv</requires>
	
	<extract file="libxml-$arch.tar.gz">$appsdir</extract>
	
	<notes>
		<center><font size="5" color="#182e7a">Libxml2 is a Library.</font></center>
		<style>
.notestable td{
background: #E6F5FF;
}

.notestable th{
background: #EFEFEF;
}
		</style>
		<table border="0" cellspacing="1" cellpadding="8" align="center" class="notestable">
			<tr>
				<td>Desc</td>
				<td>Path</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Prefix</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Binary</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/bin</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Library</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/lib</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>libxml2.so</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/lib/libxml2.so</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Libxml2</font> is the XML C parser and toolkit developed for the Gnome project (but usable outside of the Gnome platform). XML itself is a metalanguage to design markup languages, i.e. text language where semantic and structure are added to the content using extra "markup" information enclosed between angle brackets. HTML is the most well-known markup language. Though the library is written in C <a href="python.html">a variety of language bindings</a> make it available in other environments. Libxml2 is known to be very portable, the library should build and work without serious troubles on a variety of systems (Linux, Unix, Windows, CygWin, MacOS, MacOS X, RISC Os, OS/2, VMS, QNX, MVS, VxWorks, ...)
		<br /><br />
		Libxml2 is distributed under the <a href="http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.html" target="_blank">MIT License</a>
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
		This document describes libxml, the <a href="http://www.w3.org/XML/">XML</a> C parser and toolkit developed for the
		<a href="http://www.gnome.org/">Gnome</a> project. <a href="http://www.w3.org/XML/">XML is a standard</a> for building tag-based
		structured documents/data. <br/>
		Here are some key points about libxml:
		<ul><li>Libxml2 exports Push (progressive) and Pull (blocking) type parser
			interfaces for both XML and HTML.</li>
		  <li>Libxml2 can do DTD validation at parse time, using a parsed document
			instance, or with an arbitrary DTD.</li>
		  <li>Libxml2 includes complete <a href="http://www.w3.org/TR/xpath">XPath</a>, <a href="http://www.w3.org/TR/xptr">XPointer</a> and <a href="http://www.w3.org/TR/xinclude">XInclude</a> implementations.</li>
		  <li>It is written in plain C, making as few assumptions as possible, and
			sticking closely to ANSI C/POSIX for easy embedding. Works on
			Linux/Unix/Windows, ported to a number of other platforms.</li>
		  <li>Basic support for HTTP and FTP client allowing applications to fetch
			remote resources.</li>
		  <li>The design is modular, most of the extensions can be compiled out.</li>
		  <li>The internal document representation is as close as possible to the <a href="http://www.w3.org/DOM/">DOM</a> interfaces.</li>
		  <li>Libxml2 also has a <a href="http://www.megginson.com/SAX/index.html">SAX like interface</a>;
			the interface is designed to be compatible with <a href="http://www.jclark.com/xml/expat.html">Expat</a>.</li>
			</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>