<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right; margin:10px" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/CakePHP
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/frameworks/CakePHP
	</ratings>
	<space>
		15114814
	</space>
	<support>
		http://discourse.cakephp.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		3.2.10
	</version>
	<mod>71</mod>
	<mod_files>1</mod_files>
	<release_date>26-05-2016</release_date>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.5.9" />
	<requirement check="mysql" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.1.10" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="intl" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">CakePHP</font> makes building web applications simpler, faster and require less code.
		<br /><br />
		CakePHP is a rapid development framework for PHP which uses commonly known design patterns like Active Record, Association Data Mapping, Front Controller and MVC. Our primary goal is to provide a structured framework that enables PHP users at all levels to rapidly develop robust web applications, without any loss to flexibility.
		<br /><br />
		CakePHP is licensed under the <a href="http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.html" target="_blank">MIT LICENSE</a>.
		</english-overview>	
		<english-features>
	<font size="4" color="#C82334"><b>Why use CakePHP</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#BD8A5D"><b>Build Quickly</b></font><br />
<font>Use code generation and scaffolding features to rapidly build prototypes.</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#BD8A5D"><b>No Configuration</b></font><br />
<font>No complicated XML or YAML files. Just setup your database and you're ready to bake.</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#BD8A5D"><b>Friendly License</b></font><br />
<font>CakePHP is licensed under the MIT license which makes it perfect for use in commercial applications.</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#BD8A5D"><b>Batteries Included</b></font><br />
<font>The things you need are built-in. Translations, database access, caching, validation, authentication, and much more are all built into one of the original PHP MVC frameworks.</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#BD8A5D"><b>Clean MVC Conventions</b></font><br />
<font>Instead of having to plan where things go, CakePHP comes with a set of conventions to guide you in developing your application.</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#BD8A5D"><b>Secure</b></font><br />
<font>CakePHP comes with built-in tools for input validation, CSRF protection, Form tampering protection, SQL injection prevention, and XSS prevention, helping you keep your application safe &amp; secure.</font><br /><br />
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>