<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/PEEL_SHOPPING
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/ecommerce/PEEL_SHOPPING
	</ratings>
	<space>
		42560854
	</space>
	<support>
		http://forum.peel.fr/
	</support>
	<version>
		8.0.2
	</version>
	<mod>2</mod>
	<release_date>11-01-2016</release_date>
	<admin>membre.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.0.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">PEEL SHOPPING</font> is a free ecommerce CMS in PHP / MySQL, that is to say a modern and safety management tool that lets you manage your product catalog, the text on your website and everything else from a single, simple and efficient administrative interface.
		<br /><br />
		PEEL SHOPPING is released under the <a href="https://www.peel.fr/lire/licence-gpl-pour-peel-shopping-70.html" target="_blank">GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<font color="#0029A2" size="3">General Features:</font>
    <ul>
        <li>Interface Administrator to manage secure all aspects of the online shop.</li>
        <li>Ability to manage the location of the modules from the back office.</li>
        <li>Management of multiple VAT rates.</li>
        <li>Virtual Caddie allows visitors to add or remove products from their cart.</li>
        <li>Management of multiple text boxes manageable home page and other areas of the site.</li>
        <li>Management of banner ads (multiple locations)</li>
        <li>Ability to manage the Google Adsense banners.</li>
        <li>Content Management Module (unlimited number of pages)</li>
        <li>Module for generating promotional codes and value in %</li>
        <li>Ability to easily integrate Google Analythics the tag in the back office.</li>
    </ul>
    <font color="#0029A2" size="3">Product Management:</font>
    <ul>
        <li>Updating real-time product.</li>
        <li>Unlimited number of products.</li>
        <li>Number of categories and subcategories Unlimited.</li>
		<li>Possibility to place the categories and products from the back office.</li>
		<li>Ability to disable a product without deleting the profile.</li>
		<li>Choice between several system zooms highlighting the picture of your products.</li>
		<li>Management attributes "color" and "size" for product info.</li>
		<li>Management of the display of images produced by color.</li>
		<li>Ability to create any number of other attributes "options".</li>
		<li>Opportunity to showcase products on the home page of the site.</li>
    </ul>
    <font color="#0029A2" size="3">Management charges:</font>
    <ul>
        <li>Ability to have multiple type of shipment.</li>
        <li>Ability to offer shipping to customers.</li>
        <li>Calculation of shipping based on weight or the total amount of the order.</li>
        <li>Calculation of shipping depending on delivery area.</li>
        <li>Calculation of shipping depending on the type of delivery.</li>
        <li>Ability to exempt shipping when ordering over N products.</li>
    </ul>
    <font color="#0029A2" size="3">Order Management:</font>
    <ul>
        <li>Warning order confirmation email and the customer.</li>
        <li>Ability for the customer to follow an order via colissimo.</li>
		<li>Saving accounts receivable and opportunity for consultation on each sheet.</li>
		<li>Detailed overview of customer orders per customer.</li>
		<li>Issue invoices and delivery notes in PDF format.</li>
		<li>Can the customer to find his orders from their account.</li>
		<li>Can the vendor to change the terms of sale.</li>
		<li>Ability to offer its customers partial payments.</li>
		<li>Ability to view the PDF invoices from the order history.</li>
		<li>Ability to set a minimum order required.</li>
    </ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>