<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="phpScheduleIt.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Booked
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/calendars/Booked
	</ratings>
	<space>
		11961838
  	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.bookedscheduler.com/
	</support>
	<version>
		2.5.20
 	</version>
	<mod>45</mod>
	<mod_files>1</mod_files>
	<release_date>30-04-2016</release_date>
	<admin>Web/</admin>
	<min_require>2.0</min_require>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.3.0" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Booked</font> (formerly phpScheduleIt) is a simple but powerful reserve-anything scheduler. With flexible layouts, custom rules, a powerful administrative backend, and an unbelievably simple user experience, Booked can fit almost any need. From conference rooms to lab equipment to airplanes - it's Booked.
		<br /><br />
		Booked is released under the <a href="https://www.gnu.org/copyleft/gpl.html" target="_blank">GNU/GPL Version 3</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<ul>
			<li>100% free and open source.(GPL)</li>
			<li>OS independent. Only requires a web server running PHP and MySQL.</li>
			<li>Multiple languages and cultures.</li>
			<li>Simple to install in any enviornment with a web-based or manual installation process available.</li>
			<li>Easy to extend with many pluggable components.</li>
			<li>No limits when hosting on your server. Unlimited number of schedules, resources, users and reservations.</li>
			<li>Active support community.</li>
			<li>Easy to use administrative tools make it easy to quickly fine, manage and export data.</li>
			<li>Powerful reporting system.</li>
			<li>Reservation start and end reminders.</li>
			<li>Intutive click and drag schedule view allows users to quickly find and book an available time slot.</li>
			<li>Organize users and limit access by groups.</li>
			<li>Flexible layout configuration lets you set up schedules that fit your needs.</li>
			<li>Limit and control resource usage with a flexible quota system.</li>
			<li>Optionally review and approve reservation requests.</li>
			<li>Integration with Outlook®, Google® Calendar or any other system that accepts .ical files.</li>
			<li>Authentication integration with LDAP, Active Directory, WordPress and more.</li>
			<li>Customizable attributes and fields.</li>
			<li>Tiered roles and permissions.</li>
		</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>