<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.webuzo.com/sysapps/version_control/CVS
	</ratings>
	<space>
		114311168
	</space>
	<support>
		http://cvs.nongnu.org
	</support>
	<version>
		N/A
	</version>
	<mod>3</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	<release_date>N/A</release_date>
	
	<sysrequires></sysrequires>
	
	<path name="bin">/usr/bin/cvs</path>
		
	<notes>
		<center><font size="5" color="#182e7a">CVS Environment :</font></center><br />
		<style>
.notestable td{
background: #E6F5FF;
}

.notestable th{
background: #EFEFEF;
}
		</style>
		<table border="0" cellspacing="1" cellpadding="8" align="center" class="notestable">
			<tr>
				<th>Desc</th>
				<th>Path</th>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Binary</td>
				<td>/usr/bin/cvs</td>
			</tr>			
		</table>
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">CVS</font> is a version control system, an important component of Source Configuration Management (SCM). Using it, you can record the history of sources files, and documents. 
		<br /><br />
		CVS is distributed under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/gpl.html" target="_blank">GNU GPL License</a>
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
			<ul>

				<li> 
				
					It can run scripts which you can supply to log <small>CVS</small> operations or enforce 
					site-specific polices. 
				
				</li>
				<li> 
				
					<strong>Client/server <small>CVS</small></strong> enables developers scattered by geography or slow
					modems to function as a single team.  The version history is stored on
					a single central server and the client machines have a copy of all the
					files that the developers are working on.  Therefore, the network
					between the client and the server must be up to perform <small>CVS</small> operations
					(such as checkins or updates) but need not be up to edit or manipulate the
					current versions of the files.  Clients can perform all the same
					operations which
					are available locally.
				
				</li>
				<li>
				
					In cases where several developers or teams want to each maintain
					their own version of the files, because of geography and/or policy,
					<small>CVS</small>'s <strong>vendor branches</strong> can import a version from another team
					(even if they don't use <small>CVS</small>), and then <small>CVS</small> can merge the changes from
					the vendor branch with the latest files if that is what is desired.
					
				</li>
				<li>
				
					<strong>Unreserved checkouts</strong>, allowing more than one developer to work on
					the same files at the same time.
					
				</li>
				<li>
				
					<small>CVS</small> provides a flexible <strong>modules database</strong> that provides a symbolic
					mapping of names to components of a larger software distribution.  It
					applies names to collections of directories and files.  A single
					command can manipulate the entire collection.
				
				</li>
				<li> 
				
					<small>CVS</small> servers run on most unix variants, and clients for Windows
					NT/95, OS/2 and VMS are also available.  <small>CVS</small> will also operate
					in what is sometimes called server mode against local repositories on Windows
					95/NT. 
				
				</li>
				</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>