<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/XCloner
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/others/XCloner
	</ratings>
	<space>
		2278130
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.xcloner.com/support/
	</support>
	<version>
		3.5
	</version>
	<mod>2</mod>
	<release_date>24-02-2014</release_date>
	<admin>index.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.2.3" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">XCloner</font> is a professional website Backup and Restore application designed to allow you to create safe complete backups of any PHP/Mysql website and to be able to restore them anywhere. It works as a native Joomla backup component, as a native Wordpress backup plugin and also as standalone PHP/Mysql backup application.
		<br /><br />
		XCloner is released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html" target="_blank">GNU/GPL version 2</a>.
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
<h3>Complete website backup</h3>Backup your website files and databases, send them to the cloud, restore backups anywhere.
<h3>Automatic backups</h3>Create automatic backups with the built in XCloner cron script, and send them to Amazon S3.
<h3>Secure</h3>XCloner has a built in security layer to protect and easily restore your website backups.
<h3>Restore backups anywhere</h3>Easily restore backups on any location compatible with your website by using the XCloner restore.
<h3>Open Source Support</h3>XCloner works as a native Joomla backup extension, Wordpress backup plugin and Standalone website backup application.
<h3>Professional Support</h3>We offer Professional 24/7 support through the Free forums or Premium membership.
<h3>Other</h3>
<ul>
<li>Backup and Restore any PHP/Mysql  website</li>
<li>Create custom backups</li>
<li>Generate automatic backups based on cronjobs</li>
<li>Restore your backups anywhere</li>
<li>Share your custom backups with your clients</li>
<li>Store you backups on the Amazon S3 cloud</li>
<li>Backend available languages: spanish, dutch, deutsch, english, italian, polish, russian, catalan, french</li>
<li>Incremental mysql backup supporting large databases</li>
<li>Incremental file system scanning and backup supporting large websites</li>
<li>Backup Split option for environments with limited filesize</li>
<li>JQuery Start UI</li>
<li>Incremental files restore supporting large backups</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>