<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.webuzo.com/sysapps/java_tool/Clojure
	</ratings>
	<space>
		7990758
	</space>
	<support>
		http://clojure.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		1.7.0
	</version>
	<mod>3</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	<release_date>30-06-2015</release_date>
	
	<requires>java</requires>
	
	<sysrequires></sysrequires>
	
	<path name="base">/usr/local/apps/clojure</path>	
	
	<extract file="clojure-$arch.tar.gz">$appsdir</extract>
	<remove>/usr/local/apps/clojure</remove>
	
	<notes>
		<center><font size="5" color="#182e7a">Clojure Environment :</font></center><br />
		<style>
.notestable td{
background: #E6F5FF;
}

.notestable th{
background: #EFEFEF;
}
		</style>
		<table border="0" cellspacing="1" cellpadding="8" align="center" class="notestable">
			<tr>
				<th>Desc</th>
				<th>Path</th>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Base Path</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/clojure</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>jar Path</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/clojure/clojure-x.x.x.jar</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Documentation</td>
				<td>http://clojure.org/documentation</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#4f81bd">Clojure</font> is a dynamic programming language that targets the Java Virtual Machine (and the CLR, and JavaScript). It is designed to be a general-purpose language, combining the approachability and interactive development of a scripting language with an efficient and robust infrastructure for multithreaded programming. Clojure is a compiled language - it compiles directly to JVM bytecode, yet remains completely dynamic  
<br /><br />
		<br /><br />
		Clojure is distributed under the <a href="http://opensource.org/licenses/eclipse-1.0.php" target="_blank">Eclipse Public License</a>
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
			<ul>
				<li>Dynamic Development : Clojure is dynamic. That means that a Clojure program is not just something you compile and run, but something with which you can interact. </li>
				<li>Functional Programming : It provides the tools to avoid mutable state, provides functions as first-class objects, and emphasizes recursive iteration instead of side-effect based looping.</li>
				<li>Lisp : Clojure is a member of the Lisp family of languages. Many of the features of Lisp have made it into other languages, but Lisp's approach to code-as-data and its macro system still set it apart.</li>
				<li>Runtime Polymorphism : Clojure supports polymorphism at 3 levels.</li>
				<li>Concurrent Programming : Clojure simplifies multi-threaded programming in several ways. Because the core data structures are immutable, they can be shared readily between threads.</li>
				<li>Hosted on the JVM : Clojure is designed to be a hosted language, sharing the JVM type system, GC, threads etc. It compiles all functions to JVM bytecode.</li>
			</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>