<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/GLPI
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/others/GLPI
	</ratings>
	<space>
		69845933
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.glpi-project.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		0.90.3
	</version>
	<mod>31</mod>
	<release_date>11-04-2016</release_date>
	<admin>index.php</admin>
	<min_require>0.68</min_require>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.4.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="ctype" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="json" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">GLPI</font> is the Information Resource-Manager with an additional Administration- Interface.
		<br /><br />You can use it to build up a database with an inventory for your company (computer, software, printers...). It has enhanced functions to make the daily life for the administrators easier, like a job-tracking-system with mail-notification and methods to build a database with basic information about your network-topology.
		<br /><br />
		GLPI is released under the <a href="http://www.glpi-project.org/spip.php?article44" target="_blank">GNU/GPL version 2</a>.
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>General</b></font><br />
<ul>
<li>Multi-entities management (multi-park, multi-structure)</li>
<li>Multi-users management</li>
<li>Multiple Authentication System (local, LDAP, AD, Pop/Imap, CAS, x509...) and multiple servers.</li>
<li>Multilingual management</li>
<li>Permissions and profiles system </li>
<li>Pagination system </li>
<li>Configurability of display fields in lists </li>
<li>Export System in PDF, CSV, SLK (spreadsheet), PNG and SVG </li>
<li>Saving/restoration module of the database to the SQL format </li>
<li>Exportation of the database to the XML format</li>
<li>System of notifications on events (consumable stock, expiry of contracts and licenses), customizable and by entity </li>
</ul><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Inventory</b></font><br />
<ul>
<li>Import data of the inventory from one or several OCS Inventory NG servers or with the plugins FusionInventory </li>
<li>Inventory of the computers fleet with management of its components, disk space and TCO management </li>
<li>Inventory of the monitors with management of the connections to the computers </li>
<li>Inventory of the network hardware fleet with management of the connections to the devices (IP, Mac addresses, VLANs...). </li>
<li>Inventory of printers fleet with management of connections to the computers and management of consumable associated and consumption and the thresholds of alarm.</li>
<li>Inventory of the external devices (scanners, graphical tables...) with management of the connections to the computers - Inventory of the telephones fleet with management of connections to the computers </li>
<li>Inventory if the software fleet with license and expiration dates management </li>
<li>Administrative and financial Information management (purchase, guarantee and extension, damping) </li>
<li>Management of the various states for the materials (in repair...) - Management of generic peripherals and monitors being able to be associated several computers </li>
<li>Management of external bonds towards other applications </li>
<li>History of the modifications on the elements of the inventory</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>