<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Lazarus
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/guestbooks/Lazarus
	</ratings>
	<space>
		1062820
	</space>
	<support>
		http://carbonize.co.uk/Lazarus/
	</support>
	<version>
		1.24
	</version>
	<mod>32</mod>
	<mod_files>1</mod_files>
	<release_date>21-04-2015</release_date>
	<admin>admin.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.2.0" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Lazarus</font> is a free guestbook script written in PHP that uses your MySQL database for storage and is based upon the excellent Advanced Guestbook script from Proxy2.
		<br /><br />
		Lazarus has more features and several layers of anti spam protection to make one of the most feature rich and spam resistant guestbook scripts available for free.
		<br /><br />
		Lazarus is released under the <a href="http://carbonize.co.uk/Lazarus/license.php" target="_blank">GNU/GPL license</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<ul>
   <li><strong>Powerful spam fighting controls</strong>
   <ul>
      <li>Use Captcha or Saptcha to prevent automated posting</li>
      <li>Each guestbook generates a unique form</li>
      <li>Time delay before guests can post</li>

      <li>Time limit on how long a guest has to post</li>
      <li>Moderate entries before they appear in your guestbook</li>
      <li>Block or moderate posts containing bad words</li>
      <li>Ban ips or even ip blocks from posting</li>
      <li>Block posts containing to many urls</li>
   </ul>

   <br />
   </li>

   <li><strong>Apart from their name and their message your guests can tell you their...</strong>
   <ul>
      <li>Email address. You can even make email addresses required</li>
      <li>Location</li>
      <li>Website</li>

      <li>Yahoo! messenger id</li>
      <li>Live (MSN) id</li>
      <li>AIM id</li>
      <li>ICQ uin</li>
      <li>Skype id</li>
      <li>Even their gender</li>

      <li>And guests can upload an image with their posts</li>
   </ul>
   <br />
   </li>
   <li><strong>Other features</strong>
   <ul>
      <li>Powerful AGCode for formatting entries or even displaying pictures and Flash</li>

      <li>Allow HTML in entries but control which tags can be used</li>
      <li>Create thumbnails for images that have a large file size</li>
      <li>Automatic resizing of images and Flash files displayed in entries</li>
      <li>Graphical smileys (emoticons)</li>
      <li>Previewing of entries</li>
      <li>Other guests can comment on existing entries</li>

      <li>Email notification of new entries and comments</li>
      <li>Thank you email sent to guests after posting new entry</li>
      <li>Search function</li>
      <li>Email address encryption to prevent the addresses being harvested by spammers</li>
      <li>Flood controls to prevent people from flooding your guestbook with entries</li>
	</ul>

    </li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>