<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Storytlr
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/microblogs/Storytlr
	</ratings>
	<space>
		44266382
	</space>
	<support>
		http://storytlr.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		1.2.0
	</version>
	<mod>4</mod>
	<mod_files>2</mod_files>
	<release_date>20-01-2013</release_date>
	<admin>admin</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Storytlr</font> offers a single touch point for your online life in your own style. Easily post anything you find interesting, import your web 2.0 stuff and share your life online.
		<br /><br />
		Storytlr is an open source lifestreaming and micro blogging platform. You can use it for a single user or it can act as a host for many people all from the same installation.
		<br /><br />
		Storytlr is licensed under a <a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/" target="_blank">Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>

<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Import your web 2.0 life</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">Pick your sources and they will appear as a lifestream directly on your site.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Post anything you want</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">In just a few simple steps you can update your status, share a song you liked, give your opinion or link to an interesting site.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Tell your stories in a new way</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">Photo albums are old school! Pick your sources, start and end date and your story is good to go. If necessary you can tweak it for a better flow.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Choose your own style</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">Pick from a range of compelling templates that are easy to customize.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>No prominent service branding</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">It is all about you, so you will not find big logos or fixed brand colors on storytlr.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Pick or use your own domain name</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">By default you get a site on our storytlr.com domain, but you are free to use any domain you want.
</font><br /><br />
		</english-features>
		<english-exp_ad_pass>New password. Leave blank if you do not want to reset the password</english-exp_ad_pass>
		<english-err_no_username>Please provide the username to reset the password</english-err_no_username>
		<english-err_no_such_user>The Admin username is incorrect and does not exist!</english-err_no_such_user>
	</languages>
</soft>