<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.webuzo.com/sysapps/java_tools/TorqueBox
	</ratings>
	<space>
		97197761
	</space>
	<support>
		http://torquebox.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		3.1.2
	</version>
	<mod>5</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	<release_date>09-04-2015</release_date>
	
	<requires>java</requires>
		
	<sysrequires></sysrequires>
	
	<path name="base">/usr/local/apps/torquebox</path>
	<path name="bin">/usr/local/apps/torquebox/jruby/bin/torquebox</path>
	<path name="conf">/usr/local/apps/torquebox/jboss/standalone/configuration/standalone.xml</path>	
	
	<extract file="torquebox-$arch.tar.gz">$appsdir</extract>
	
	<remove>/usr/local/apps/torquebox</remove>
	
	<is_default>106_1</is_default>
	<is_default>109_1</is_default>
	<is_default>123_1</is_default>		
	
	<notes>
		<center><font size="5" color="#182e7a">TorqueBox Environment :</font></center><br />
		<style>
.notestable td{
background: #E6F5FF;
}

.notestable th{
background: #EFEFEF;
}
		</style>
		<table border="0" cellspacing="1" cellpadding="8" align="center" class="notestable">
			<tr>
				<th>Desc</th>
				<th>Path</th>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Base Path</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/torquebox</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Bin path</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/torquebox/jruby/bin/torquebox</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Documentation</td>
				<td>http://torquebox.org/documentation/</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">TorqueBox</font> is a new kind of Ruby application platform that supports popular technologies such as Ruby on Rails and Sinatra, while extending the footprint of Ruby applications to include built-in support for services such as messaging, scheduling, caching, and daemons.

TorqueBox provides an all-in-one environment, built upon the latest JBoss AS Java application server and JRuby. Functionality such as clustering, load-balancing and high-availability is included right out-of-the-box.

<br /><br />
		<br /><br />
		TorqueBox is distributed under the dual licensed <a href="http://torquebox.org/license-lgpl.txt" target="_blank">GNU Lesser General Public License</a> and <a href="http://torquebox.org/license-mit.txt" target="_blank">MIT License</a>
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
			<h1 id="rack">Rack</h1>			
			<p>TorqueBox supports Rack, including Rails 2.3.x, 
			Rails 3.x, Sinatra, and others.  Rack applications are served 
			as first-class resources within the web container. The web container is clusterable, and web sessions may 
			be shared between nodes without any additional configuration.</p>			
			<h1 id="jdbc">JDBC</h1>			
			<p>High-performance tried-and-true Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) database drivers power your ActiveRecord and
			other database access.</p>			
			<h1 id="daemons">Daemons</h1>			
			<p>TorqueBox provides the framework to manage your daemon-like Ruby components.  TorqueBox
			makes sure it starts and stops with your application.  What you do in the middle is
			up to you.</p>			
			<h1 id="scheduled-jobs">Scheduled Jobs</h1>			
			<p>Cron-like functionality is provided by the TorqueBox server. Job classes implemented in Ruby have full access 
			to to your Ruby environment and are managed by a durable job scheduler.</p>			
			<h1 id="messaging">Messaging</h1>			
			<p>Your simple Ruby components can both produce and consume messages from 
			clustered and distributed asynchronous messaging fabric powered by HornetQ.</p>			
			<h1 id="asynchronous-tasks">Asynchronous Tasks</h1>
			<p>Leveraging the messaging system, TorqueBox makes it easy to execute simple
			tasks and methods asynchronously, allows your application to quickly return
			control to the user.</p>	
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>