<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/XMS
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/others/XMS
	</ratings>
	<space>
		1065541
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.aws-dms.com
	</support>
	<version>
		5.0.4
	</version>
	<mod>4</mod>
	<release_date>13-05-2015</release_date>
	<admin>index.php?use=templates/designer.xml</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.4.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="xsl" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">XMS</font> is Easy, almost everything on the web is xml, isn't it? This opens new ways of using data, I mean everything on the internet can be considered a datasource, and there are plenty of them. 
		<br /><br />
		XMS is an online visual web development enviroment and framework, providing a web application base, with multi language support, based on XML.
		<br /><br />
		XMS is released under the <a href="http://www.aws-dms.com/GPL.TXT" target="_blank">GNU General Public License</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<ul>
	<li><font color="#176BBD" size="2">Aws Designer: One tool for all operations</font>
	<ul>
		<li>Build applications</li>
		<li>Create multi language support</li>
		<li>Create / edit configuration</li>
		<li>Template generator and editor</li>
		<li>Bulk processing</li>
		<li>Even create you own rss news</li>
	</ul>
	</li><br />
	<li><font color="#176BBD" size="2">Onsite programming</font>
	<ul>
		<li>Using aws Designer you can create new applications or edit existing ones remotely, without using special software or any other resource.</li>
		<li>You can even use a public computer, log into designer on your site and move on.</li>
	</ul>
	</li><br />
	<li><font color="#176BBD" size="2">More data sources</font>
	<ul>
		<li>Any html/xml page on your site, or anywhere on internet, can be used as data source.</li>
	</ul>
	</li><br />
	<li><font color="#176BBD" size="2">Less study</font>
	<ul>
		<li>You don't need to spend too much time learning dozens of classes, functions and browsing a bushy documentation.</li>
		<li>You only have to understand how an aws application is working (takes less that 10 minutes) and use Designer rules manager to build a new application.</li>
		<li>Can be easily used with any other framework and most of the time only basics of php coding is enough; In addition this software provides a "visual" framework (directives and filters) and only two classes awsXML (for xml files/datasources) and awsHTML (for html files/datasources)</li>
	</ul>
	</li><br />
	<li><font color="#176BBD" size="2">Templates generated automatically</font>
	<ul>
		<li>You don't have to loose time building templates, because Designer does this for you!!</li>
		<li>With simply one click of a button you can import any html page from your mockup or anywhere on the web.</li>
	</ul>
	</li><br />
	<li><font color="#176BBD" size="2">Easy to extend</font>
	<ul>
		<li>You can define your own directives in application processor.</li>
	</ul>
	</li><br />
	<li><font color="#176BBD" size="2">Easy to share</font>
	<ul>
		<li>Each application can be used as code library or templates container.</li>
	</ul>
	</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>