<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Admidio
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/projectman/Admidio
	</ratings>
	<space>
		15228076
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.admidio.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		3.1.3
	</version>
	<mod>23</mod>
	<release_date>16-04-2016</release_date>
	<admin>adm_program/system/login.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.3.7" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Admidio</font> is a free online membership management, optimized for clubs, groups and organizations. It consists of classical management members from a variety of modules that can be installed and adjusted to a new or existing website. 
		<br /><br />
		Registered users have your website by Admidio including access to predefined and user-configurable membership lists, people profiles and an Agenda. In addition, members may be pooled in groups are assigned properties and search for it.
		<br /><br />
		Admidio is released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html" target="_blank">GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<ul> 
	<li>
		Access control (protects data from the eyes of unauthorized members)<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Freely configurable membership lists<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Export of all lists to Excel, OpenOffice or as a CSV file<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Appointment and announcement management with iCal export<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Free configuration of groups, departments and Features<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Individual rights assignment to groups, departments and Features<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Upload, manage, and view photos in a photo gallery<br /><br />
	</li>  
	<li> 
		Profile fields can be configured<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Adjusting the layout with the help of different Plugins<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Access to a database of several organizations and member data<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Guestbook with commenting capability for all entries<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		Import new users from a CSV file<br /><br />
	</li> 
	<li> 
		and much more ...
	</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
		<english-short_site_name>Short name</english-short_site_name>
		<english-exp_short_site_name>Maximum 10 characters</english-exp_short_site_name>
	</languages>
</soft>