<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.webuzo.com/sysapps/stacks/LAMP
	</ratings>
	<space>
		N/A
	</space>
	<support>
		N/A
	</support>
	<version>
		N/A
	</version>
	<mod>4</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	
	<notes>
		The LAMP Stack is basically intalling the apps listed alongside. It quickly installs the Apache , MySQL and PHP environment necessary for development.
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">LAMP</font> is a combination of free, open source software. The acronym LAMP refers to the first letters of Linux (Operating system), Apache HTTP Server, MySQL (database software), and PHP, PERL or Python, principal components to build a viable general purpose web server.<br /><br />
		LAMP has become a de facto development standard. Today, the products that make up the LAMP stack are included by default in nearly all Linux distributions, and together they make a powerful web application platform. 
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
			<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b> Linux</b></font><br /><br />
			Linux is free open-source software which means the source code is available for the operating system, which can be edited according to specific needs.<br /><br /><br />
			
			<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b> Apache</b></font><br /><br />
			Apache is an open source web server, the most popular in use.<br /><br />
			
			<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b> MySQL</b></font><br /><br />
			MySQL is a multithreaded, multi-user, SQL database management system (DBMS) now owned by Oracle Corporation.<br /><br />
			
			<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b> PHP</b></font><br /><br />
			PHP is a reflective programming language originally designed for producing dynamic web pages. PHP is used mainly in server-side application software. Perl and Python can be used similarly..<br /><br />
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>