<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/SeoToaster_CMS
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/cms/SeoToaster_CMS
	</ratings>
	<space>
		58750601
	</space>
	<support>
		http://forum.seotoaster.com/
	</support>
	<version>
		2.5.0
	</version>
	<mod>5</mod>
	<mod_files>1</mod_files>
	<release_date>01-03-2016</release_date>
	<admin>go</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.3.3" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="PDO" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="gd" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="zip" /> 
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="json" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">SeoToaster CMS</font> is the most advanced SEO &amp; marketing website building &amp; management system that can be used right out of the box, with no plug-ins required. SeoToaster combines in one package a full blown CMS, but also a private area membership system, a blog that complies with Google News &amp; Yahoo News requirements, and a responsive mobile wireframe for building websites.<br /><br />
		 SeoToaster CMS features a uniquely intuitive content management system interface, combined with powerful automated marketing such as web-to-call, automated SMS and email marketing.  
		<br /><br />
		SeoToaster CMS is released under <a href="http://www.seotoaster.com/seotoaster-license.html" target="_blank">GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE V3</a>.
		</english-overview>			
		<english-features>
		<b>Innovative Features for Everyone :</b><br/><br/>
		
<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Simplified yet powerful website edition</font></strong> : <br /> Click and edit content right on your web pages. Your content is saved automatically.<br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Integrated membership system</font></strong> :<br /> Protect access to private information in 1 click. Great for non-profit &amp; membership organizations.<br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Integrated blog system</font></strong> :<br /> SeoToaster helps you get your site featured in Yahoo news &amp; Google news by meeting all technical requirements.<br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Native SEO, Mobile, Local &amp; Social functions</font></strong> :<br /> SeoToaster generates geo-localization file for mobile &amp; local search, and let you publish your updates to Twitter, LinkedIn and Facebook wall &amp; pages in 1 click.<br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Built-in tripwire web form protections</font></strong> : <br /> to prevent bots to spam your email without interfering with conversion objectives, as sometimes Recaptcha does. <br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Connected &amp; social</font></strong> :<br /> Automated Google webmaster tools, real-time analytics, brand monitoring &amp; social network marketing with a free cloud based SeoSamba account. <br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Centralized management for multi-websites owners</font></strong> :<br /> Manage &amp; automate SEO, social networking and online marketing across any number of websites through a centralized interface. <br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Mobile responsive wireframe</font></strong> :<br />The ultimate tool to streamline responsive website building with SeoToaster for web designers &amp; web developers. <br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Strict W3C compliance</font></strong> :<br /> Get maximum website performance with search engines as SeoToaster and all marketplace vetted plug-ins produce strictly W3C-compliant code. <br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">APPS</font></strong> :<br /> A cloud-based service that connect web forms with functionalities such as email marketing. An entirely new way to add functionalities from the cloud and switch services provider with no plug-in tinkering. <br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Built-in media servers</font></strong> :<br /> providing up to five-times faster web serving leveraging modern web browser parallel download capabilities. <br /><br />

<strong><font size="2" color="#215A93">Specialized inline editor types</font></strong> :<br /> Build unbreakable website themes by defining website areas functions (imageonly, textonly, videonly etc…). Great to minimize headaches and support calls. <br /><br />

		</english-features>
		<english-special_character>Spaces and Special characters are not allowed for</english-special_character>
	</languages>
</soft>