<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/GRAV
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/cms/GRAV
	</ratings>
	<space>
		13768239
	</space>
	<support>
		http://getgrav.org/forum
	</support>
	<version>
	   1.0.10
	</version>
	<mod>3</mod>
	<mod_files>1</mod_files>
	<release_date>11-02-2016</release_date>
	<admin>admin</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.5.9" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="gd" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="zip" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="openssl" />
 	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Grav</font> is a Fast, Simple, and Flexible file-based Web-platform. Although Grav follows principles similar to other flat-file CMS platforms, it has a different design philosophy than most. The underlying architecture of Grav is built using well established and best-in-class technologies. 
		<br /><br />
		Grav is released under the <a href="https://github.com/getgrav/grav/blob/develop/LICENSE.txt" target="_blank">MIT License</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<ul>
	<li><b>Fast</b> : Performance is not just an afterthought, we baked it in from the start</li>
	<li><b>Extensible</b> : Grav has a powerful API and sophisticated Package Manager to make it super flexible</li>
	<li><b>Enjoyable Content Creation</b> : Use your favorite Markdown editor to create your content online or offline</li>
	<li><b>Stellar Performance</b> : Grav intelligently caches content to deliver great performance, regardless of hosting</li>
	<li><b>Powerful Content Filtering</b> : Create unlimited taxonomies such as tags, categories, and authors to filter and manage your content</li>
	<li><b>Dynamic Content Types</b> : The flat-file nature of Grav lets you define custom fields for any of your pages, including modular content</li>
	<li><b>Simple Backups and Restores</b> : Being file based means backing up and restoring your data is super easy, and changing hosts/servers is a breeze</li>
	<li><b>Image Media Processing</b> : Dynamic image manipulation to resize, crop, resample, and effects all with automatic caching of images</li>
	<li><b>Easy Theme Customization</b> : No need to start from scratch, use Theme Inheritance and then modify the bits you need, allowing for easier update</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
			<english-err_alphanumpass8>Password must contain at least one number and one uppercase and lowercase letter, and at least 8 or more characters</english-err_alphanumpass8>
			<english-err_username>Username requires only lowercase chars, numbers, underscore and dash.</english-err_username>
	</languages>
</soft>