<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right; margin:10px" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Adminer
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/dbtools/Adminer
	</ratings>
	<space>
		423994
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.adminer.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		4.2.5
	</version>
	<mod>28</mod>
	<release_date>01-06-2016</release_date>
	<admin>adminer.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Adminer</font> is a full-featured database management tool written in PHP.
		<br /><br />
		Conversely to phpMyAdmin, Adminer consist of a single file ready to deploy to the target server. Adminer is available for MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MS SQL and Oracle.
		<br /><br />
		Adminer is released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.txt" target="_blank">GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<ul>
<li>Connect to a database server with username and password</li>
<li>Select an existing database or create a new one</li>
<li>List fields, indexes, foreign keys and triggers of table</li>
<li>Change name, engine, collation, auto_increment and comment of table</li>
<li>Alter name, type, collation, comment and default values of columns</li>
<li>Add and drop tables and columns</li>
<li>Create, alter, drop and search by indexes including fulltext</li>
<li>Create, alter, drop and link lists by foreign keys</li>
<li>Create, alter, drop and select from views</li>
<li>Create, alter, drop and call stored procedures and functions</li>
<li>Create, alter and drop triggers</li>
<li>List data in tables with search, aggregate, sort and limit results</li>
<li>Insert new records, update and delete the existing ones</li>
<li>Supports all data types, blobs through file transfer</li>
<li>Execute any SQL command from a text field or a file</li>
<li>Export table structure, data, views, routines, databases to SQL or CSV</li>
<li>Alter export for projecting changes to production database</li>
<li>Print database schema connected by foreign keys</li>
<li>Show processes and kill them</li>
<li>Display users and rights and change them</li>
<li>Display variables with links to documentation</li>
<li>Manage events and table partitions (MySQL 5.1)</li>
<li>Schemas, sequences, user types (PostgreSQL)</li>
<li>Extensive customization options</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>