<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.webuzo.com/sysapps/java_tools/Railo
	</ratings>
	<space>
		220286976
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.getrailo.com/
	</support>
	<version>
		4.2.1.008
	</version>
	<mod>3</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	<release_date>16-05-2014</release_date>
	
	<requires>java</requires>
	
	<path name="base">/usr/local/apps/railo</path>
	
	<extract file="railo-$arch.tar.gz">$appsdir</extract>
	
	<remove>/usr/local/apps/railo</remove>
	
	<notes>
		<center><font size="5" color="#182e7a">Railo Environment :</font></center><br />
		<style>
.notestable td{
background: #E6F5FF;
}

.notestable th{
background: #EFEFEF;
}
		</style>
		<table border="0" cellspacing="1" cellpadding="8" align="center" class="notestable">
			<tr>
				<th>Desc</th>
				<th>Path</th>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Base Path</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/railo</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Documentation</td>
				<td>http://www.getrailo.org/index.cfm/documentation/</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Railo Server</font> commonly referred to as Railo (/raɪloʊ/ raɪ-lo), is open source software which implements the general-purpose CFML server-side scripting language, often used to create dynamic websites, web applications and intranet systems. CFML is a dynamic language supporting multiple programming paradigms and runs on the Java Virtual Machine (JVM).
<br /><br />
		<br /><br />
		Railo is distributed under the  <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LGPL" target="_blank">LGPL License</a>
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
			<ul>
				<li>Supports programming with inheritance, mixins and metaclasses.</li>
				<li>Dynamic typing and duck typing.</li>
				<li>Literal notation for arrays and structs.</li>
				<li>Embedding variables in strings.</li>
				<li>Named arguments, optional arguments, and default arguments.</li>
				<li>Three levels of object variable scope: This (object public), Variables (object private), Local (function private).</li>
				<li>Multiple global variable scope: Request, Session, Client, Application, Server, Cluster.</li>
				<li>Distinct user-provided variable scopes: Form (post), Url (get), Cookie, CGI.</li>
				<li>Automatic garbage collection, (via JVM).</li>
				<li>Global and local exception handling, (via onError and try/catch.)</li>
				<li>Custom dispatch behaviour (through onMissingMethod and implicit getters and setters).</li>
				<li>Implicit object conversion (through _toString, _toNumeric, _toBoolean, _toDate). </li>
				<li>Native threads.</li>
				<li>Support for, multiple character encodings, and i18n.</li>
				<li>Large standard library, covering common web development needs.</li>
				<li>Native handling for easily creating and consuming web services.</li>
				<li>Separate GUI Administrators for individual web contexts, plus a global server administrator.</li>
				<li>All admin settings configurable programmatically, or via editing XML config files.</li>
				<li>Native resources for all built-in filesystem tags and functions.</li>
				<li>Clustering and Synchronization for both traditional and cloud servers.</li>
				<li>Task Manager for scheduling repeated actions, or re-trying failed events.</li>
				<li>Native support for Hibernate ORM.</li>
				<li>Large number of image manipulation functions.</li>
				<li>Event Gateways for asynchronous code execution.</li>
				<li>Native session management (CFML sessions or J2EE sessions) with onSessionStart and onSessionEnd triggers.</li>
				<li>Built-in user authentication and roles functionality.</li>
			</ul>  
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>