<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/miniBB
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/forums/miniBB
	</ratings>
	<space>
		597562
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.minibb.com/forums/
	</support>
	<version>
		3.2.1
	</version>
	<mod>10</mod>
	<release_date>21-10-2015</release_date>
	<admin>bb_admin.php?</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">miniBB</font> is a standalone, open source program for building your own Internet forum.
		<br /><br />
		If you want a lite, simple and stable message board attached to your existing website at the very high integration level, 
		which may include the full customization of the layout to the look of your website, or even synchronizing with the existing membership system, 
		you've just came across to the best forum solution for such purpose available worldwide.
		<br /><br />
		miniBB is released under <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/old-licenses/gpl-2.0.html" target="_blank">GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<br /><br />
<font size="3" color="#1281B6"><b>Security</b></font><br />
		<ul>
			<li>Protected members passwords</li>
			<li>Flood protection by the IP-address and time</li>
			<li>Your board may be securely opened even for guest posting! - with the special Captcha module protection on guest posting and new registrations.</li>
			<li>Special rules for guests and new users for posting external links on forum </li>
			<li>Safe auto-login when returning on forum in X hours</li>
			<li>Single super-admin account for better security</li>
			<li>Email verification on registration</li>
			<li>Full HTTP Secure (HTTPS) Compatibility</li>
		</ul>
<font size="3" color="#1281B6"><b>Members Profiles and related</b></font><br />
		<ul>
			<li>Unlimited amount of member accounts</li>
			<li>Forum-related statistics and graphs, based on the amount of posts for each user</li>
			<li>Member Photos</li>
			<li>Possibility to extend member profiles with any kind of custom fields</li>
			<li>Private Messaging and communication between forum members, with the optional Email notification when the new PM arrives; as well as "Reminders" feature (PM to yourself)</li>
			<li>Contacting members by email sent through the server</li>
		</ul>
<font size="3" color="#1281B6"><b>Search Engine Optimization</b></font><br />
		<ul>
			<li>Fully valid W3C XHTML 1.0 Transitional HTML, ultra-compact, printing-ready and indexing-friendly output</li>
			<li>SEO Friendly URLs</li>
			<li>Automatic Description META-tags for forum and topic pages</li>
			<li>Dynamic INDEX, FOLLOW (NOINDEX, NOFOLLOW) META-tags</li>
			<li>Automatic "nofollow" tag on external hyperlinks, and automatic "follow" tag on internal forum and website domain URLs</li>
			<li>RSS feed</li>
		</ul>
<font size="3" color="#1281B6"><b>Administrative Settings</b></font><br />
		<ul>
			<li>Creating and managing forum titles, descriptions, icons</li>
			<li>Assigning private, read-only or replies-only forums</li>
			<li>Protecting whole forum by a single password</li>
			<li>Banning users by IP/username or blocking user accounts</li>
			<li>IP tracking in messages (for administrative staff only)</li>
			<li>Members search (by email, username, activity etc.)</li>
		</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>