<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Fork
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/cms/Fork
	</ratings>
	<space>
		69106906
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.fork-cms.com/community
	</support>
	<version>
		4.0.0
	</version>
	<mod>55</mod>
	<release_date>27-05-2016</release_date>
	<admin>private/</admin>
	<min_require>4.0.0</min_require>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.5.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="curl" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="dom" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="libxml" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="SimpleXML" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="SPL" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="json" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="iconv" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Fork</font> is an open source CMS that will rock your world.
		<br /><br />
		Fork CMS is dedicated to creating a user friendly environment to build, monitor and update your website. 
		Fork takes great pride in being the Content Management System of choice for beginners and professionals.
		<br /><br />
		The License for Fork is available <a href="https://github.com/forkcms/forkcms/blob/master/LICENSE.md" target="_blank">here</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>An intuitive and user friendly interface</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">Fork combines this grand vision with the latest technological innovations to allow developers, front-end developers and designers to build kick-ass websites. 
This makes Fork CMS next in line for world domination.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Powerful apps that deliver</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">Fork CMS is jam-packed with cool apps. It's comes with the territory of being a kick-ass Content Management System. 
And just in case you want even more, you can download additional apps to expand your site.<br /><br />
Fork is constantly working with their dedicated community to build new and exciting apps. Keep an eye on their blog on to get updates on our brand spanking new modules.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Killer themes that make an impression</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">Fork believes that a good site should look that way too. That's why they have a wide collection of beautiful themes built by kick-ass designers.
Fork is constantly working with their talented community to build new themes. Keep an eye on their blog on to get updates on stunning new themes.
</font><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>A marketing monster that's here to help</b></font><br /><br />
<font size="1">With Fork CMS, being a marketing guru is super easy. Find out what drives your visitors and optimise your site accordingly. 
Did they mention that Search Engines love Fork CMS too?<br /><br />
Fork CMS offers powerful tools for both beginners and professionals. Fork CMS also plays nicely with existing services like Campaign Monitor and Google Analytics.
</font>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>