<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.webuzo.com/sysapps/databases/Redis
	</ratings>
	<space>
		5215536
	</space>
	<support>
		http://redis.io/support
	</support>
	<version>
		2.8.21
	</version>
	<mod>3</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	<release_date>04-06-2015</release_date>
	
	<path name="base">/usr/local/apps/redis</path>
	
	<extract file="redis-$arch.tar.gz">$appsdir</extract>
	
	<remove>/usr/local/apps/Redis</remove>
	
	<notes>
		<center><font size="5" color="#182e7a">Redis Environment :</font></center><br />
		<style>
.notestable td{
background: #E6F5FF;
}

.notestable th{
background: #EFEFEF;
}
		</style>
		<table border="0" cellspacing="1" cellpadding="8" align="center" class="notestable">
			<tr>
				<th>Desc</th>
				<th>Path</th>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Base Path</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/redis</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Documentation</td>
				<td>http://redis.io/documentation</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Commands</td>
				<td>http://redis.io/commands</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Redis</font> is an open source, BSD licensed, advanced key-value store. It is often referred to as a data structure server since keys can contain strings, hashes, lists, sets and sorted sets. 
<br /><br />
		Redis is distributed under three clause <a href="http://redis.io/topics/license" target="_blank">BSD license</a>
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
			<p>You can run atomic operations on these types, like appending to a string; incrementing the value in a hash; pushing to a list; computing set intersection, union and difference; or getting the member with highest ranking in a sorted set.</p>
			
			<p>In order to achieve its outstanding performance, Redis works with an in-memory dataset. Depending on your use case, you can persist it either by dumping the dataset to disk every once in a while, or by appending each command to a log.</p>
			
			<p>Redis also supports trivial-to-setup master-slave replication, with very fast non-blocking first synchronization, auto-reconnection on net split and so forth.</p>
			
			<p>Other features include Transactions, Pub/Sub, Lua scripting, Keys with a limited time-to-live, and configuration settings to make Redis behave like a cache.</p>
			
			<p>You can use Redis from most programming languages out there.</p>
			
			<p>Redis is written in ANSI C and works in most POSIX systems like Linux, *BSD, OS X without external dependencies. Linux and OSX are the two operating systems where Redis is developed and more tested, and we recommend using Linux for deploying. Redis may work in Solaris-derived systems like SmartOS, but the support is best effort</p>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>