<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/SLiMS
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/others/SLiMS
	</ratings>
	<space>
		28585352
	</space>
	<support>
		http://forum.slims.web.id/
	</support>
	<version>
		8.2
	</version>
	<mod>4</mod>
	<release_date>07-03-2016</release_date>
	<admin>index.php?p=login</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.5.0" />
	<requirement check="mysql" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.0.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="gd" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mysqli" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">SLiMS</font> (Senayan Library Management System) is a free and open source Library Management System. It is build on free and open source technology like PHP and MySQL.<br /><br />
		 SLiMS provides many features such as bibliography database, circulation, membership management and many more that will help "automating"  library tasks.  
		<br /><br />
		SLiMS is licensed under <a href="http://slims.web.id/web/?q=license" target="_blank">GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE V3</a>.
		</english-overview>			
		<english-features>
		<ul><font size="2">
<li>Online Public Access Catalog (OPAC) with thumbnail document image support (can be use for book cover), Simple Search and Advanced Search mode</li>
<li>Digital contents/files (PDF, DOC, RTF, XLS, PPT, Video, Audio, etc.) attachment in each bibliographic record support</li>
<li>Documents record detail in MODS (Metadata Object Description Schema) XML format</li>
<li>RSS (Really Simple Syndication) XML format for OPAC</li>
<li>OAI-PMH (Open Archives Initiative Protocol for Metadata Harvesting) in Dublin Core format for metadata harvesting purpose</li>
<li>Bibliographic/catalog database management with book cover image support</li>
<li>Serial publication control</li>
<li>Document items (book copies) management with barcode support</li>
<li>Master Files management to manages document referential data such as GMD, Collection Types, Publishers, Authors, Locations, Authors and Suppliers</li>
<li>Circulation support with following sub-features :
<ul>
<li>Loan and Return transaction</li>
<li>Collections reservation</li>
<li>Quick return</li>
<li>Configurable and flexible Loan Rules</li>
<li>Membership management</li>
<li>Stock Taking module to help Stock Op name process in library</li>
<li>Reporting and Statistics</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>System modules with following sub-features :
<ul>
<li>Global system configuration</li>
<li>Modules management</li>
<li>Application Users and Groups management</li>
<li>Holiday settings</li>
<li>Barcodes generator utility</li>
<li>Database backup utility</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Responsive user interface</li>
<li>3rd party bibliographic records indexing support with Sphinx Search and MongoDB</li>
</font></ul>
		</english-features>
		<english-special_character>Spaces and Special characters are not allowed for</english-special_character>
	</languages>
</soft>