<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Jamroom
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/cms/Jamroom
	</ratings>
	<space>
		29077540
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.jamroom.net/the-jamroom-network/forum
	</support>
	<version>
		5.3.5
	</version>
	<mod>45</mod>
	<release_date>03-05-2016</release_date>
	<admin>user/login</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.3.0" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="gd" />
	<requirement check="php" type="extension" name="mbstring" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Jamroom</font> is a community content management system. It enables you to bring your entire community online to participate in your websites content creation.
		<br /><br />
		If you want to build an online community where everyone has their own identity then Jamroom can provide you with the tools to do it.
		Jamroom is licensed under the <a href="http://www.mozilla.org/MPL/2.0/" target="_blank">Mozilla Public License (MPL), version 2.0</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>100% Your Branding and Control</b></font><br /><br />
Jamroom 5 is a "White Label" Social Media System - Jamroom code runs on <b>your server, and is 100% under your control.</b>
<ul>
	<li>All logos and images are easily changed to your logos and images.</li>
	<li>Templates and CSS are 100% customizable to your site design and colors.</li>
	<li>No fees for "logo removal" or other silly charges.</li>
</ul>
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Extensive Profile features</b></font><br /><br />
Jamroom 5 is a <b>profile centered</b> system based around user generated content: 
<ul>
	<li>Flexible profiles featuring both group and individual aspects.</li>
	<li>Twitter™ like Activity Stream and Follower System makes "friends" easy.</li>
	<li>Build your community on user provided content like blogs, audio, video and forums.</li>
</ul>
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Easy to expand and customize</b></font><br /><br />
Jamroom 5 makes it <b>easy to add new features</b> and customize your site to suit your community needs. 
<ul>
	<li>Install dozens of modules and features with 1 click using the Jamroom Marketplace.</li>
	<li>Powerful online editors for customizing images, templates and styles.</li>
	<li>Flexible template based design makes it easy to tweak the site to suit your needs.</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>