<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/ArticleSetup
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/others/ArticleSetup
	</ratings>
	<space>
		5259615
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.articlesetup.com
	</support>
	<version>
		1.00
	</version>
	<mod>2</mod>
	<mod_files>3</mod_files>
	<admin>admin</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.5.4
	</softversion>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">ArticleSetup</font> is the powerful, flexible, and surprisingly simple web software that you can use to setup your own article directory website.
		<br /><br />
		This premium script is easy to use, customizable, feature-rich, fully supported and best of all, it's completely free - forever.
		<br /><br />
		ArticleSetup is the free PHP article directory script that allows you to publish articles submitted by authors; similar to EzineArticles or ArticleBase. 
		<br /><br />
		ArticleSetup is released under their Custom License which allows to redistribute.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Clean, Customizable Design</b></font><br /><br />
<font>The front-end of your directory exudes professionalism and polish. The design puts content, navigation, and superb ad placement in focus for your visitors.</font>
<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Powerful Admin Panel</b></font><br /><br />
<font>The administration area was built with speed and usability in mind. Everything you need to manage and monitor your directory is at your fingertips.</font>
<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Insightful Author Dashboard</b></font><br /><br />
<font>Allow your users/authors to create an account, update their profiles, submit new articles, manage existing articles and more - you have complete control.</font>
<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>All About the Articles</b></font><br /><br />
<font>Articles are the heart of your directory, and they couldn't be easier to manage. Approve pending articles, mark as "problem", create, view, sort and search.</font>
<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Total Settings Control</b></font><br /><br />
<font>The site settings area of your admin panel allows full control - without the clutter. Set the min/max words per article, manage email notifications, upload a logo, and more.</font>
<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Category Management</b></font><br /><br />
<font>Add, delete, rename and move categories (and subcategories) in a snap. Plus, your directory comes pre-loaded with 200 of the most popular categories.</font>
<br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Admin Features</b></font>
<ul>
<li>Guided interface with concise tips throughout</li>
<li>Article control: create, edit, approve, delete, and more</li>
<li>Author management: view, ban, restore</li>
<li>Pages: Create static pages for the front-end</li>
<li>Category editor: full control with 200+ pre-installed</li>
<li>Manage ad codes and placements</li>
<li>Total site control: templates, settings, logo, and more</li>
</ul><br /><br />
<font size="2" color="#1281B6"><b>Front-End Features</b></font>
<ul>
<li>Powerful template engine with easy-to-edit HTML designs</li>
<li>Comments - allow visitors to leave their feedback</li>
<li>Built-in RSS Feeds for the homepage and categories</li>
<li>Author profile pages with url, bio and articles</li>
<li>Social share buttons on each article</li>
<li>Intuitive navigation/pagination controls</li>
<li>Automatic search optimization and SEO-friendly URLs</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>