<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.png" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/GPixPixel
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/admanager/GPixPixel
	</ratings>
	<space>
		6311805
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.tufat.com/s_milliondollarhomepage.htm
	</support>
	<version>
		1.4.1
	</version>
	<mod>2</mod>
	<mod_files>5</mod_files>
	<admin>admin/index.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">GPixPixel</font> is a FREE yet powerful million pixel script, based on the popular marketing concept. 
		<br /><br />
		Advanced settings include, among others, the ability to use interlaced images, temporarily take the site down for maintenance and put it back online when all changes are done, and enable/disable blog comments. 
		<br /><br />
Multiple payment modules available for pixel purchasing, including Authorize.Net, PayPal, NOCHEX, PSiGates, and others. More are being added all the time. PayPal IPN is fully supported, too!
		<br /><br />
		GPixPixel is licensed under the <a href="www.gnu.org/licenses/lgpl-2.1.html" target="_blank">GNU Lesser General Public License</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
		<ul>
<li>Advanced "lasso" feature for pixel selection.</li>
<li>Pixel List feature provides a quick view of all purchased regions.</li>
<li>Advanced settings manager to maintain database-stored site settings.</li>
<li>All pages are fully XHTML transitional compliant, checked against W3C standards.</li>
<li>Multi-language e-mail template editor allows quick and convenient editing of confirmation e-mails.</li>
<li>Payment History manager shows you a list of received payments, and any payment errors.</li>
<li>Language editor permits you to easily add new languages to your million pixel ad site.</li>
<li>Manage multiple grids, set the price per grid, set the grid background and line colors, delete grids, etc.</li>
<li>Blog feature, with optional commenting. Security measures have been added to the blog comments section to help ward off script daemons that may try to spam your site.</li>
<li>Image library is available (with more images being added all the time) for users who may not have a pre-defined image to use with your million pixel ad website.</li>
<li>Newsletter templates, fully editable using the FCKEditor, are available in the admin panel. Send your users announcements of updates and new features in your system.</li>
<li>Quickly e-mail all pixel owners with a single click (the "Pixel Owners" link at the right), using the newsletter feature.</li>
<li>Pixel zoom feature allows your site visitors to more easily view small pixel regions.</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
		<english-exp_ad_pass>New password. Leave blank if you do not want to reset the password</english-exp_ad_pass>
		<english-err_no_username>Please provide the username to reset the password</english-err_no_username>
		<english-err_no_such_user>The Admin username is incorrect and does not exist!</english-err_no_such_user>
	</languages>
</soft>