<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/eyeOS
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/projectman/eyeOS
	</ratings>
	<space>
		48953754
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.eyeos.org/
	</support>
	<version>
		2.5
	</version>
	<mod>6</mod>
	<mod_files>5</mod_files>
	<admin>index.php</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<requirement check="php" type="version" operator="ge" value="5.3" />
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">eyeOS </font> is a disruptive desktop entirely usable from a  web browser. It includes an office suite and some collaboration  aplications, as well as a full framework to develop new web apps as if they were desktop apps.
		<br /><br />
		 Free and Open Source so you can host your own system, keeping all your data under your control.
		<br /><br />
		eyeOS is released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/agpl-3.0.txt">GNU Affero General Public License version 3</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<ul>
<li><strong>Ubiquity:</strong> Access your documents, files and applications from anywhere and any device.</li>
<li><strong>Flexibility:</strong> From the small business to the big corporation. Also for individual use. There is an eyeOS for you!</li>
<li><strong>Integration:</strong> The eyeOS architecture makes easier and faster the integration of any web application that you use.</li>
<li><strong>Simplicity:</strong> From its first steps, eyeOS has been planned and created to be intuitive and easy to use.</li>
<li><strong>Collaboration:</strong> Share files and edit them in a real-time collaboration suite with other users.</li>
<li><strong>Privacy:</strong> Decide where your files are: You can have your own eyeOS server!</li>
<li><strong>Security:</strong> Control your eyeOS. You are who manage roles and permissions for each user.</li>
<li><strong>Low costs:</strong> All in one in a single platform: the best way to optimize time and resources.</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
		<english-exp_ad_pass>New password. Leave blank if you do not want to reset the password</english-exp_ad_pass>
		<english-err_no_username>Please provide the username to reset the password</english-err_no_username>
		<english-err_no_such_user>The Admin username is incorrect and does not exist!</english-err_no_such_user>
	</languages>
</soft>