<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;margin:10px;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<demo>
		http://www.softaculous.com/demos/Open_Conference_Systems
	</demo>
	<ratings>
		http://www.softaculous.com/softwares/others/Open_Conference_Systems
	</ratings>
	<space>
		23146825
	</space>
	<support>
		http://pkp.sfu.ca/ocs
	</support>
	<version>
		2.3.6.0
	</version>
	<mod>2</mod>
	<release_date>28-05-2014</release_date>
	<admin>index.php/index/index/login</admin>
	<softversion>
		4.1.7
	</softversion>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">Open Conference Systems (OCS)</font> is a free Web publishing tool that will create a complete Web presence for your scholarly conference.
		<br /><br />Open Conference Systems (OCS) is an open source solution to managing and publishing scholarly conferences online. OCS is a highly flexible management and publishing system that can be downloaded for free and installed on a local Web server. 
		<br /><br />It has been designed to reduce the time and energy devoted to the clerical and managerial tasks associated with managing a conference, while improving the record-keeping and efficiency of editorial processes. 
		<br /><br />It seeks to improve the scholarly and public quality of conference publishing through a number of innovations, from making policies more transparent to improving indexing.
		<br /><br />
		Open Conference Systems (OCS) is released under the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/gpl.html" target="_blank">GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE</a>.
		</english-overview>		
		<english-features>
<font size="3" color="#182e7a">OCS will allow you to:</font>
<ul>
<li>create a conference Web site </li>
<li>compose and send a call for papers</li>
<li>electronically accept paper and abstract submissions</li>
<li>allow paper submitters to edit their work</li>
<li>post conference proceedings and papers in a searchable format</li>
<li>post, if you wish, the original data sets</li>
<li>register participants</li>
<li>integrate post-conference online discussions</li>
</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>