<soft xmlns="http://www.softaculous.com">
	<overview>
		<img src="logo.gif" style="float:right;" alt="" />{{overview}}
	</overview>
	<features>
		{{features}}
	</features>
	<ratings>
		http://www.webuzo.com/sysapps/utilities/ImageMagick
	</ratings>
	<space>
		48010766
	</space>
	<support>
		http://www.imagemagick.org/index.php
	</support>
	<version>
		6.9.1-6
	</version>
	<mod>2</mod>
	<softversion>
		4.1.9
	</softversion>
	<major>1</major>
	
	<release_date>13-06-2015</release_date>
		
	<path name="base">/usr/local/apps/imagemagick</path>
	<path name="bin">/usr/local/apps/imagemagick/bin/Magick-config</path>
	<extract file="imagemagick-$arch.tar.gz">$appsdir</extract>
	
	<remove>/usr/local/apps/imagemagick</remove>	
	
	<notes>
		<center><font size="5" color="#182e7a">ImageMagick Environment :</font></center><br />
		<style>
.notestable td{
background: #E6F5FF;
}

.notestable th{
background: #EFEFEF;
}
		</style>
		<table border="0" cellspacing="1" cellpadding="8" align="center" class="notestable">
			<tr>
				<th>Desc</th>
				<th>Path</th>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Base</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/imagemagick</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Server Binary</td>
				<td>/usr/local/apps/imagemagick/bin/Magick-config</td>
			</tr>
			
		</table>
	</notes>
	<languages>
		<english-overview>
		<font size="5" color="#182e7a">ImageMagick</font> is a software suite to create, edit, compose, or convert bitmap images. It can read and write images in a variety of formats (over 100) including DPX, EXR, GIF, JPEG, JPEG-2000, PDF, PNG, Postscript, SVG, and TIFF. Use ImageMagick to resize, flip, mirror, rotate, distort, shear and transform images, adjust image colors, apply various special effects, or draw text, lines, polygons, ellipses and Bézier curves.
		<br /><br />
		ImageMagick is distributed under the <a href="http://www.imagemagick.org/script/license.php" target="_blank">Apache 2.0 license,</a>
		</english-overview>
		<english-features>
			
			<ul>
				<li>Format conversion: convert an image from one format to another (e.g. PNG to JPEG).</li>
				<li>Transform: resize, rotate, crop, flip or trim an image.</li>
				<li>Transparency: render portions of an image invisible.</li>
				<li>Draw: add shapes or text to an image.</li>
				<li>Decorate: add a border or frame to an image.</li>
				<li>Special effects: blur, sharpen, threshold, or tint an image.</li>
				<li>Animation: create a GIF animation sequence from a group of images.</li>
				<li>Text and comments: insert descriptive or artistic text in an image.</li>
				<li>Image identification: describe the format and attributes of an image.</li>
				<li>Composite: overlap one image over another.</li>
				<li>Montage: juxtapose image thumbnails on an image canvas.</li>
				<li>Generalized pixel distortion: correct for, or induce image distortions including perspective.</li>
				<li>Morphology of shapes: extract features, describe shapes, and recognize patterns in images.</li>
				<li>Delineate image features: Canny edge detection, mean-shift, Hough lines.</li>
				<li>Motion picture support: read and write the common image formats used in digital film work.</li>
				<li>Image calculator: apply a mathematical expression to an image or image channels.</li>
				<li>Discrete Fourier transform: implements the forward and inverse <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Discrete_Fourier_transform">DFT</a>.</li>
				<li>Perceptual hash: map visually identical images to the same or similar hash-- useful in image retrieval, authentication, indexing, or copy detection as well as digital watermarking.</li>
				<li>Color management: accurate color management with color profiles or in lieu of-- built-in gamma compression or expansion as demanded by the colorspace.</li>
				<li>High dynamic-range images: accurately represent the wide range of intensity levels found in real scenes ranging from the brightest direct sunlight to the deepest darkest shadows.</li>
				<li>Encipher or decipher an image: convert ordinary images into unintelligible gibberish and back again.</li>
				<li>Virtual pixel support: convenient access to pixels outside the image region.</li>
				<li>Large image support: read, process, or write mega-, giga-, or tera-pixel image sizes.</li>
				<li>Threads of execution support: ImageMagick is thread safe and most internal algorithms execute in parallel to take advantage of speed-ups offered by multicore processor chips.</li>
				<li>Distributed pixel cache: offload intermediate pixel storage to one or more remote servers.</li>
				<li>Heterogeneous distributed processing: certain algorithms are OpenCL-enabled to take advantage of speed-ups offered by executing in concert across heterogeneous platforms consisting of CPUs, GPUs, and other processors.</li>
				<li>ImageMagick on the iPhone: convert, edit, or compose images on your iOS device such as the iPhone or iPad.</li>
			</ul>
		</english-features>
	</languages>
</soft>